<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on inspiredbits</title>
    <link>https://inspiredbits.org/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on inspiredbits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Original-Theme is licensed with the Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 11:47:45 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://inspiredbits.org/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Hugo Dev Server From Any Device On The Same Network</title>
      <link>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/access-hugo-dev-server-from-network-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 11:47:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/access-hugo-dev-server-from-network-computers/</guid>
      <description>So while developing themes or testing different layouts we might need to test the website on multiple devices and different form-factors. Running command Hugo server by default is not accessible over the network on different devices like your smartphone or tablet.
In order to access the website from other devices we need to bind the server to its network interface IP (instead of the loopback IP i.e. 127.0.0.1) using the &amp;ndash;bind argument.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Configure Hugo Site With Github Pages for Custom Domain</title>
      <link>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/how-to-configure-hugo-site-with-github-pages-for-custom-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 09:59:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/how-to-configure-hugo-site-with-github-pages-for-custom-domain/</guid>
      <description>Hosting a static site on Github is pretty easy but there are some obscure configurations needed to get everything setup properly. This post walks through few of those for setting up hugo generated site with Github.
Hugo&amp;rsquo;s official documentation on how to Host on GitHub has almost all the details that is required to configure Hugo and successfully host your static website on GitHub Pages. I got lost in the custom domain step on which the page does not have much details, except setting up the CNAME file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highlight Active Nav Menu in Hugo</title>
      <link>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/highlight-active-nav-menu-in-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 17:38:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inspiredbits.org/blog/highlight-active-nav-menu-in-hugo/</guid>
      <description>How to highlight the current tab in Hugo theme</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>